Guide to the Olan D. Forker papers, 1950-2000.
Forker, Olan D. papers, 1950-2000
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Olan D. Forker papers, 1950-2000.
21-1-3444
Olan D. Forker
1.3 cubic ft.
Scrapbooks, Diaries, Reports, Correspondence, and Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains journals, bound volumes of works by Prof. Forker, subject files and correspondence.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Prof. Forker taught in the Department of Applied Economics and Management in the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains journals, vita, bound volumes of works by Prof. Forker, subject files and correspondence.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Forker, Olan D.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Dept. of Applied Economics and Management.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Travel
Series II. Reports and Publications
Series III. Subject Files
Series IV. Scrapbook
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Travel
  - Travel Journal, Historical Record (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Diary: Trip to Japan, 10/4-18/1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Log: Trip to Japan, 2/27/1990 - 3/30/1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Travel Journal: Spain, Germany, Brussels, 8/24/1985 - 10/7/1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Report on Visit to Turkey, May and June 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Turkey Aid Mission, 8/1/1970 - 7/31/1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Series II. Reports and Publications
  - Agriculture Price Policy in Turkey, A Collection of Works (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Trip Reports: Vegetable Production and the Dehydration Industry (Box 1, Folder 8a)
  - Appendices for Vegetable Production (Box 1, Folder 8b)
- Series III. Subject Files
  - Correspondence: Plans after Chairmanship, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Director of T.M.O. Turkey Karaelmas, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Universal Food Corp. Letter of Appointment, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Universal Food Corp. By-Laws, Articles of Corp., 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sabattical: University of Manchester, England, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hospital Committee Chair, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Agriculture Economics Faculty Wives Notes, 1968-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Universal Foods Corp. Annual Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Speeches: University of Naples, Sept. 10, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Presentation: Gödöllö University, Hungary, 10/14/1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Series IV. Scrapbook
  - Scrapbook, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Personal Scrapbook, Ag. Ext. Service, University of California, 1/1/1961 - 12/7/1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Personal Scrapbook, Ag. Ext. Service, University of California, 2/9/1962 - 12/31/1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Personal Scrapbook, Ag. Ext. Service, University of California, 1/1/1963 - 12/31/1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Personal Scrapbook, Agri. Economist, AES University of California Berkley Jan. 1, 1964 - Dec. 31, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Personal Scrapbook, University of California Berkley, WEMC, Subcommittee on Livestock and Diaries, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Personal Scrapbook, Ext. Economist, Jan. 1, 1965 - Dec. 31, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Personal Scrapbook, Ag. Ext. Service, University of California, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Personal Scrapbook, Jan. 1, 1966 - Dec. 31, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Personal Scrapbook, 1969 - 1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Diary Book, 1973 - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)